Given a non negative integer number num. For every numbers i in the range 0 ≤ i ≤ num calculate the number of 1's in their binary representation and return them as an array.

Example:
For num = 5 you should return [0,1,1,2,1,2].

Follow up:

    It is very easy to come up with a solution with run time O(n*sizeof(integer)). But can you do it in linear time O(n) /possibly in a single pass?
    Space complexity should be O(n).
    Can you do it like a boss? Do it without using any builtin function like __builtin_popcount in c++ or in any other lang